Guide to the Mann Library records, 1908-2011.
Mann Library records, 1908-2011
- Series I. Correspondence, General
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Office of Foreign Agricultural Relations, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Bureau of Foreign and Domestic Commerce, 1925-1950 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Foreign Economic Administration, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Bureau of Home Economics, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Interstate Commmerce Commission, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Bureau of Investigation and Research, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Labor, 1933-1951 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Mines, 1944-1948 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Office of Price Administration, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1943-1944 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Soils, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Superintendent of Documents, 1936-1951 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Tariff Commission, 1936-1947 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Treasury Department, 1945-1946 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-War Food Administration, 1944-1945 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Office of War Information, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence-Territories and Possessions-United States-Work Progress Administration, 1944-1948 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence-North America-British Guiana, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence-North America-Canada, 1938-1952 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence-North America-Mexico, 1945-1948 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence-South America-Argentina, 1944-1948 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence-South America-Brazil, 1927-1950 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence-South America-Chile, 1944-1950 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence-South America-Columbia, 1944-1947 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence-South America-Nicaragua, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence-South America-Peru, 1942-1952 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Belguim, 1928-1947 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Czechoslovak Republic, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Denmark, 1925-1948 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Finland, 1942-1947 (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence-Europe-France, 1945-1948 (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Germany, 1939-1952 (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Germany-Paul Paray, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Great Britain-England, 1927-1952 (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Great Britain-Wales, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Greece, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Hungary, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Italy, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Letvia, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Netherlands, 1933-1948 (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Norway, 1947-1948 (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Poland, 1939-1950 (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Portugal, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Russia, 1928-1929 (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Spain, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Sweden, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Switzerland, 1946-1948 (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence-Europe-Yugoslavia, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence-Asia-China, 1929-1949 (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence-Asia-India, 1927-1945 (Box 40, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence-Asia-Korea, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence-Tel Aviv-Palestine, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence-South Africa, 1931-1948 (Box 40, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence-Oceanica-Australia, 1928-1950 (Box 40, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence-Oceanica-New Zealand, 1943-1944 (Box 40, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence-Information Requested by Borrowers, 1950-1951 (Box 40, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence-No Reply Required, 1950-1952 (Box 40, Folder 87)
  - Exchange agreement forms completed by libraries in Great Britain, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Exchange agreement forms completed by libraries in France, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Exchange agreement forms completed by libraries in Japan, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Exchange agreement forms completed by libraries in Japan, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "A", 1952-1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "A", 1950-1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "A", 1950-1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "A", 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "A", 1950-1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "A", 1971-1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "A", 1950-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "B", 1950-1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "B", 1950-1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "B", 1950-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "B", 1950-1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "B", 1950-1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "C", 1950-1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "C", 1950-1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "C", 1950-1960 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "C", 1950-1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "C", 1953-1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "C", 1957-1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "C", 1951-1965 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "D", 1949-1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "E", 1949-1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "E", 1949-1965 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "E", 1945-1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "E", 1949-1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "F", 1949-1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "F", 1942-1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "F", 1950-1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "F", 1944-1963 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "F", 1946-1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "G", 1950-1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "G", 1950-1965 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "G", 1954-1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "G", 1950-1965 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "H", 1947-1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "H", 1945-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "H", 1950-1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "I", 1950-1971 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "I", 1950-1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "I", 1950-1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "I", 1949-1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "I", 1950-1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "I", 1950-1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "I", 1950-1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "I", 1952-1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "J", 1951-1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "J", 1950-1971 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "K-L", 1953-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "M", 1950-1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "M", 1951-1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "N", 1947-1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "N", 1950-1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "N", 1950-1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "P", 1950-1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "P", 1950-1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "P", 1950-1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "P", 1948-1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "P", 1950-1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "R", 1950-1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "R", 1957-1968 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "S", 1950-1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "S", 1950-1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "S", 1950-1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "S", 1950-1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "S", 1950-1979 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "T", 1950-1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "T", 1950-1979 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1951-1971 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1956-1972 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1957-1967 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1956-1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1956-1971 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1963-1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1946-1964 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1942-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1951-1958 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1954-1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1956-1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1956-1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1950-1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1963-1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1963-1966 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "U", 1963-1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "V", 1952-1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "V", 1943-1962 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "V", 1952-1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "V", 1958-1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "W", 1950-1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "Y", 1951-1964 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "Y", 1951-1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence- Acquisitions Department - "Z", 1950-1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence- Gifts and Exchange - "A-C", 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence- Gifts and Exchange - "E-I", 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence- Gifts and Exchange - "J-P", 1979-1985 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence- Gifts and Exchange - "Q-U", 1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence- Gifts and Exchange - "V-Z", 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence- Domestic Pending - "A-Z", 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Serial subscriptions for exchange partners, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence- "A-C", 1977-1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence - "C-D", 1978-1985 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence- "E-G", 1976-1985 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence- "H thru I", 1971-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence- "J thru M", 1973-1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence- "N thru P", 1974-1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence- "S thru U", 1966-1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence- "U thru Z", 1972-1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Exchange Form Letters - Brazil, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Exchange Form Letters - Germany, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Memos - Baylor University, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Circulation-Memos, Correspondence, Reports, 1953-1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Circulation-Memos, Correspondence, Reports, 1967-1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Circulation-Memos, Correspondence, Reports, 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - C.U. Library Automation-Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - C.U. Library Automation-Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Mann Library Circulation-Notes, Correspondence, Reports, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - EDUCOM (Interuniversity Communications Council), 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - EDUCOM-Meeting Minutes of the NAL Network Advisory Committee, Memos, Reports, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Rice Library-Correspondence, 1949-1957 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Rice Library-Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Rice Library-Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Rice Library-Correspondence, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Rice Library-Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Rice Library-Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Rice Library-Correspondence, 1969-1978 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Rice Collections Operations-Correspondence, Reports, 1950-1981 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Olnay Brown Kent-Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Rice Requests to Complete Collection-Correspondence, 1956-1977 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Rice Publications-Publication #1, Correspondence, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Rice Publications-Publication #2, Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Rice Publications-Publication #3, Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence-Joe F. Pehringer (Rice), 1961-1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence-Joe F. Pehringer (Rice), 1969-1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - South Central Research Library Council (SCRLC)- Correspondence, Minutes, Memos, 1969-1983 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Woollen, Sellman-Class of 1914, Correspondence, Articles, 1960-1982 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Ellis Room-Correspondence, Memos, Notes, Data, 1969-1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Gifts to Mann Library-Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Gifts to Mann Library- Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - African Document Delivery-Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Philippines, University of-Correspondence, Memos, 1956-1965 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Philippines, University of-Correspondence, Memos, 1965-1977 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Powell Reception and Memorial, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Mann Library-Interlibrary Loan, Correspondence, Memos, 1966-1978 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Mann Library-Interlibrary Loan, Correspondence, Memos, 1981-1985 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Mann Library-Reference,Staff Meetings, Minutes, Reports, Memos (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Agronomy Library-Memo, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - BIOSIS (Biological Abstracts)-Correspondence, 1988-1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - BRS Information Technologies (Correspondence), 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - CGIAR-Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Dean David Call-Correspondence, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Suggestions and Comments (Correspondence), 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Statements - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - CALS AGET-Advisory Group on Electronic Technology (Reports, Correspondence), 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - CALS AGET-Advisory Group on Electronic Technology (Reports, Correspondence), 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Bond University-Donald Watts (Correspondence), 1989 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - China- Memos, Notes, Memos, 1980-1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Chemistry Online Retrieval Experiment (CORE)- Correspondence, Memos, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - CORE-Correspondence, Memos, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - CUL Facilities Planning-Memos, Minutes, Notes, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - CUL Facilities Planning-Memos, Minutes, Notes, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Herrnstadt, Mary; Monroe-Woodbury School-IBM Proposal, Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - International Agricultural Development (IAD)- Correspondence, Memos, 1976-1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - IAD-Correspondence, Memos, 1962-1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - International Agriculture-Memos, Reports, Seminars, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - International Agriculture-Correspondence, Chinese, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - International Agriculture-Correspondence, Memos, Reports, Philippines VISCA, 1983-1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - International Agriculture-Correspondence, Reports, Philippines, 1981-1984 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - International Agriculture-Correspondence, Reports, Philippines, 1981-1984 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - International Conference-Correspondence, Memos, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Lovercheck, Charles L, Attorney-Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Mann Library Booksale, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Mann Library Collection Analysis-Correspondence, Memos, 1983-1988 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Mann Library Committee-Correspondence, Memos, Minutes, 1949-1960 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Mann Library Committee-Correspondence, Memos, Minutes, 1961-1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Mann Library Committee-Correspondence, Memos, Minutes, 1981-1989 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Mann Library Administrative Council-Minutes, 1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Mann Library Administrative Council-Minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Janet McCue Appointment Book, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Series II. Correspondence, Sam Demas Day Files
  - Sam Demas- Day File (Associate Librarian), 1983-01-1983-10, Pt. 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Sam Demas- Day File (Associate Librarian), 1983-01-1983-10, Pt. 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Sam Demas- Day File (Associate Librarian), 1983-10-1983-12 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Sam Demas- Day File (Associate Librarian), 1984-01-1984-07, Pt. 1 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Sam Demas- Day File (Associate Librarian), 1984-01-1984-07, Pt. 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Sam Demas- Day File (Associate Librarian), 1984-07-1985-03, Pt. 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Sam Demas- Day File (Associate Librarian), 1984-07-1985-03, Pt. 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Sam Demas- Day File (Associate Librarian), 1985-04-1985-11-04 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Sam Demas- Day Files (Associate Librarian), 1988-10-1989-04 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Notis Fund Accounting, 1990-09-21-1990-11-03 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Sam Demas-Appointment Book, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Series III. Correspondence, Jan Olsen Appointment Books and Day Files
  - Jan Olsen's Papers, 1989-1992 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Jan Olsen's Papers, 1988,1989 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Conferences, Programs, Presentations (Jan Olsen), 1989-1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Uganda Trip-Jan Olsen, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Jan Olsen Appointment Book, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Appointment Book [no owner name written in front], 1983 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Jan Olsen Appointment Book, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jan Olsen Appointment Book, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Jan Olsen Appointment Book, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Jan Olsen Appointment Book, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Jan Olsen Appointment Book, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Jan Olsen Appointment Book, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Jan Olsen Appointment Book, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Jan Olsen Appointment Book, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Jan Olsen Appointment Book, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Jan Olsen Appointment Book, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Jan Olsen Appointment Book, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Appointment Book [no owner name written in front], 1994 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Appointment Book [no owner name written in front], 1995 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Appointment Book [no owner name written in front], 1996 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Appointment Book [no owner name written in front], 1997 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Appointment Book [no owner name written in front], 1999 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence (Pt. 1), 1982-02-1982-12 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence (Pt. 2), 1982-02-1982-12 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1983-01-1983-03 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1983-04-1983-06- (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1983-07-1983-12 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1984-01-1984-06 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1984-07-1984-12 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1985-01-1985-12 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1986-01-1986-06 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence (Pt. 1), 1986-07-01-1987-06-20 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence (Pt. 2), 1986-07-01-1987-06-30 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence (Pt. 1), 1987-07-01-1988-06-30 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence (Pt. 2), 1987-07-01-1988-06-30 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence (Pt. 1), 1988-07-01-1989-06-30 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence (Pt. 2), 1988-07-01-1989-06-30 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1989-07-01-1990-06-30 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence (Pt. 1), 1990-07-01-1991-06-30 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence (Pt. 2), 1990-07-1991-06-30 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1991-06-1992-06 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1992-06-1993-06 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1993-06-1994-06 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1994-07-1995-06 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1995-07-1996-05 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Jan Olsen, Director-Day File, Correspondence, 1996-07-1998-03 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Automation Project-Daybook, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Automation Daybook II, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Series IV. Budget
  - Library Accounts, 1910-1911 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Library Accounts, 1911-1912 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Library Accounts, 1912-1913 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Library Accounts, 1913-1914 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Library Accounts, 1914-1915 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Library Charges, 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Book Orders, 1916 (Box 36, Folder 4)